Mss.B.St15
American Philosophical Society
- Correspondence
  - Letter to J[acob] Stauffer, March 24, 1875; 8x5; Williamson, John, 1826-1885.
    Livingston, Ky; A.L.S. 4p. Mutilated. Concerning natural history.
  - Letter to [Jacob Stauffer], May 13, 1875; 8x5; Porter, Thomas Conrad, 1822-1901
    Easton, A.L.S. 2p., end. Mutilated. Concerning botany. Refers to Asa Gray.
  - Letter to Jacob Stuaffer, Lancaster, Aug. 15, 1876; 10x7-1/2; Baird, Spencer F[ullerton], 1823-1887.
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p., add., end. Mutilated. Friendly letter. Refers to Henry.
  - Letter to [Jacob Stauffer], May 16, 1878; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Ryder, John Adam, 1852-1895
    A.L.S. 3p. and end. Mutilated. Concerning fossils.
  - Letter to [Jacob] Stauffer, June 11, 1878; 8x5; Cope, E. D. (Edward Drinker), 1840-1897
    A.L.S. 1p. and end. Concerning blind fishes. Concerning invertebra.
  - Letter to J[acob] Stauffer, Jan. 25, 1879; 10x8; Bean, Tarleton H. (Tarleton Hoffman), 1846-1916
    Washington, A.L.S. 1p.with a sketch on the reverse of the page. Mutilated. Concerning snakes. Refers to Cope and Baird.
  - Letter to Jacob Stuaffer, Lancaster, Feb. 12, 1879; 10-1/2x8; Baird, Spencer F[ullerton], 1823-1887.
    Washington, A.L.S. 1p. and end. Mutilated. Concerning fishes.
  - Letter to Jacob Stauffer, Lancaster, Feb. 13, 1879; 10x8; Bean, Tarleton H. (Tarleton Hoffman), 1846-1916
  - Letter to Jacob Stauffer, Lancaster, March 10, 1879; 10x8; Bean, Tarleton H. (Tarleton Hoffman), 1846-1916
    Washington, A.L.S. 1p. and end. Mutilated. Concerning fishes. Refers to Baird.
  - Letter to Jacob Stauffer, Aug. 5, 1879; 8x5; Mather, Fred, 1833-1900
    Newark, A.L.S. 2p. Mutilated. Business.
  - Letter to J[acob] Stauffer, Aug. 11, 1879; 10x8; Hoffman, Walter James, 1846-1899
    Washington, A.L.S. 2p., end. Mutilated. Forwards publications to him and to the Linnean Society.
  - Letter to [Jacob Stauffer], Feb. 8; 7-1/2x5; Morris, John G., (John Gottlieb), 1803-1895
    Baltimore, A.L.S. 4p. Mutilated. Concerning insects. Refers to Say.
  - Letter to [Jacob Stauffer], June 23; 7-1/2x5; Morris, John G., (John Gottlieb), 1803-1895
    Baltimore, A.L.S. 3p.and end. Friendly letter. Refers to Bancroft, Henry and Gray.
  - Letter to [Jacob Stauffer], July 27; 9x7; Loring, Charles G. (Charles Greely), 1794-1867
    Boston, A.L.S. 1p. Mutilated. Concerning Asa Gray.
  - Letter to J[acob] Stauffer, Sept. 29; 8x5; Saxton, Charles Maurice, 1812-1888
    New York, A.L.S. 1p. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Jacob Stauffer], Oct. 3; 8x5; Farlow, W. G. (William Gilson), 1844-1919
    Boston, A.L.S. 2p.,end. Mutilated. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Jacob Stauffer], Oct. 18; 8x5; Farlow, W. G. (William Gilson), 1844-1919
    Boston, A.L.S. 3p.and end. Concerning fungi.
  - Letter to Jacob Stauffer, Lancaster, undated; 4-1/2x5-1/2; Baird, Spencer Fullerton, 1823-1887
    A.L.S. 1p. Fragment. Refers to Cope. Concerning the salamander.
  - Letter to [Jacob] Stauffer., undated; 8x5; Carman, Elbert S.
    A.L.S. 2p. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Jacob Stauffer], undated; 8x5; Farlow, W. G. (William Gilson), 1844-1919
    Cambridge. A.L.S. 2p.,end. Concerning fungi.
  - Letter to E. C. Reigart., After 1839, March 7; 8x5; Darlington, Edward, 1795-1884
    Letter from the Historical Agricultural and Mechanical Insitute of Lancaster
    A.L.S.: Edw. C. Darlington. 1p.with 2p.enc. Agrees to merge library with the Athenaeum and forwards extracts from the minutes.
  - Letter to [Jacob Stauffer], undated; 8x5; Morris, John G., (John Gottlieb), 1803-1895
    Lancaster, Wednesday morning. A.L.S. 2p.and end. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Jacob] Stauffer., undated; 6x5; Rathvon, S. S., (Simon Snyder), 1812-1891
    A.L.S. 2p.,end. Concerning entomology.
  - Letter to [Jacob Stauffer?]., undated; 10-1/2x8; Robinson, John
    A.L.S. 1p.and end. Mutilated. Incomplete. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Jacob Stauffer]., undated; 8x5; Smith, J. Jay, (John Jay), 1798-1881
    A.L.S. 1p. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to Jacob Stauffer., undated; 8x5; Smith, J. Jay, (John Jay), 1798-1881
    A.L.S. 1p. Business.
  - Letter to [Jacob] Stauffer., undated; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Smith, J. Jay, (John Jay), 1798-1881
    A.L.S. 1p. Mutilated. Friendly letter.
  - Autobiographical sketch, undated; 10x7-1/2; Stauffer, Jacob, b. 1808
    Mt. Joy. A.D. 2p. Mutilated. Ruminations about his life, including the fact that he has not been able to generate a decent income. Hope to find womeone who will pay for his publication.